<?xml version='1.0' encoding='ISO-8859-1'?>
<texturePropertyList>
	<property name='color'>
		<description>
			Defines the color of a material. The color is used for various lighting steps.
			Typically this property is specified using a 24-bit image.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='color.gamma'>
		<description>
			Defines the gamma correction for the color property.
			Typically used for images which have a particular gamma value.
		</description>
		<type>color</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>2.2</red>
			<green>2.2</green>
			<blue>2.2</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='color.tint'>
		<description>
			Defines a color used to tint the color property. This defines an 3-component color
			that is multiplied component wise with the color property. Typically used to create
			tinted versions of a texture without creating multiple skins.
		</description>
		<type>color</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>1</red>
			<green>1</green>
			<blue>1</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='color.tint.mask'>
		<description>
			Defines a mask for the color.tint property. This defines an 1-component image
			that blends between color.tint and color property. Typically used to create tinted
			versions of a texture where only individual parts of the texture are tinted without
			creating multiple skins. A value of 1 applies the color.tint which is the default.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='color.solidity.multiplier'>
		<description>Defines the color weight factor for solidity. This texture property is
			used with decal textures to weight the decal color against the color of the
			underlaying geometry. This allows to create decals where not all texture properties
			affect the underlaying geometry the same way in respect to the decal solidity.
			A value of 0 makes the decal to not affect the underlaying geometry color at all.
			A value of 1 makes the decal fully overwrite the underlaying geometry color.
			Values in between blend linearly the decal color  with the underlaying geometry
			color. The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='color.omnidir'>
		<description>
			Defines the omni-directional color of a material using a cube map. This
			property is used only by sky layers, sky bodies, lights and environment map probes.
			The property has to contain image data with depth of 6. Each layer represents one
			face in the cube map: X+, X-, Y+, Y-, Z+ and Z- (in this order). Typically this
			property is specified using a 24-bit image of depth 6.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='color.omnidir.equirect'>
		<description>
			Defines the omni-directional color of a material using an equirectangular map.
			This property is used only by sky layers, sky bodies, lights and environment map probes.
			The image data defined by the property has to be formatted in the equirectangular format.
			Typically this property is specified using a 24-bit image.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='ambient.occlusion'>
		<description>
			Defines the ambient occlusion. This simulates the effect of indirect lighting where
			locations on a model are darker inside cavities. Values range from 0 to 1 where 0 is
			fully occluded and 1 is fully in light. In general fully in light equals to full light
			contribution and fully occluded to zero light contribution. In general this property
			affects indirect lighting but can also affect direct lighting at the description of
			the graphic module.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='ambient.occlusion.solidity.multiplier'>
		<description>
			Defines the ambient occlusion weight factor for solidity. This texture property is
			used with decal textures to weight the decal ambient occlusion against the ambient
			occlusion of the underlaying geometry. This allows to create decals where not all
			texture properties affect the underlaying geometry the same way in respect to the
			decal solidity. A value of 0 makes the decal to not affect the underlaying geometry
			ambient occlusion at all. A value of 1 makes the decal fully overwrite the
			underlaying geometry ambient occlusion. Values in between blend linearly the decal
			ambient occlusion  with the underlaying geometry ambient occlusion.
			The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='normal'>
		<description>
			Defines the normal of the surface. This is a special texture property in that the
			color is not a real color but a normal encoded as a color. Normal maps are used to
			fake detail on flat surfaces by specifying the structure of normals along a surface.
			<br/><br/>
			The normal is encoded as a 24-bit color relative to the tangent space of the surface.
			The tangent space is formed taking the original triangle normal and the tangent which
			points along the U direction of triangle.
			<br/><br/>
			The red component indicates the X component of the normal (along the U direction of
			the texture). Negative values are in the range from 0 to 0.5 and positive values in
			the range from 0.5 to 1.
			<br/><br/>
			The green component indicates the Y component of the normal (along the V direction
			of the texture). Negative values are in the range from 0 to 0.5 and positive values
			in the range from 0.5 to 1.
			<br/><br/>
			The blue component indicates the Z component of the normal (along the triangle normal).
			Negative values are in the range from 0 to 0.5 and positive values in the range from
			0.5 to 1.
			<br/><br/>
			The normal is normalized before storing. Normals should not point further away than
			90 degree measured from the triangle normal. If you go beyond this limit render
			artifacts can occur. Due to this layout normal maps have a tendency to be blueish in
			color since the Z component is always positive.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0.5</red>
			<green>0.5</green>
			<blue>1</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='normal.strength'>
		<description>
			Defines the strength of the normal map. This property blends the normal obtained from
			the normal map with the real geometry normal. This allows to use the full image
			resolution for normal map details where subtle normal map effects are desired without
			producing artifacts. Furthermore this can also be used to create dynamic normal map
			effects without the need for a dynamic normal map property. A value of 0 uses the
			real geometry normal. A value of 1 uses the normal obtained from the "normal" texture
			property. Values in between blend linearly between the two normals. The default value
			is 1 to apply the full normal map value.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='normal.solidity.multiplier'>
		<description>
			Defines the normal weight factor for solidity. This texture property is used with
			decal textures to weight the decal normal against the normal of the underlaying
			geometry. This allows to create decals where not all texture properties affect the
			underlaying geometry the same way in respect to the decal solidity. A value of 0 makes
			the decal to not affect the underlaying geometry normal at all. A value of 1 makes the
			decal fully overwrite the underlaying geometry normal. Values in between blend
			linearly the decal normal with the underlaying geometry normal.
			The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='height'>
		<description>
			Defines the height of the surface. This is also a special texture property similar
			to the normal map one but this time the height of a surface relative to the mesh
			surface is stored. This height can be used for different purpose depending on the
			graphic module used. One usage is to derive a normal map from the height difference.
			Another usage is to dynamically increase the detail level of a mesh. The new vertices
			are then offset using this height. Terrain meshes can also use this height information
			to provide LODing (level of detail reduction over distance). A value of 0.5 indicates
			no surface height alteration. Values below 0.5 indicate a dent in a surface while
			values above 0.5 indicate a bump in a surface. The strength and offset of the height
			alteration can be set using the "height.scale" and "height.offset" property.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0.5</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='height.scale'>
		<description>
			Used in conjunction with the height surface property and defines the scaling of the
			height values. With a scaling of 1 the height values are considered to be in the range
			of -0.5m to 0.5m. The height texture property values are multiplied by the scale factor
			and offseted by the offset factor resulting in the final height values. For generating
			normal maps this is not required. As an example if the hills and valleys are at most
			1cm then a scaling of 0.02 (1 divided by 50) has to be used (0.5m times 0.02 yields
			0.01m or 1cm). This property has to be a single value.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0.1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='height.offset'>
		<description>
			Used in conjunction with the height surface property and defines the relative offset
			of the height values. Positive values move the height values away from the surface
			while negative values move them into the surface. This can be used for height maps
			only denting into or only bumping out of the surface to maximize the texture
			resolution. The effective offset added to the height is the height.offset multiplied
			by the height.scale. The height.offset can thus be considered the percentage shift
			of the height texture property values. The typical range is from -0.5 (height of 1
			is surface level and 0 the total bottom) to 0.5 (height of 0 is surface level and 1
			the total uphill). For generating normal maps this is not required. This property
			has to be a single value.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='transparency'>
		<description>
			Defines the transparency material. Transparent materials allow to see through with
			varying strength. Transparent material is still solid unless the solidity texture
			property is used. Hence a material can be fully transparent with a value of 0 but at
			grazing angles the material still behaves like a mirror due to fresnel and physically
			based rendering. For truely stopping light to interact with the material use the
			solidity texture property instead. Use this texture property for all kinds of glass
			type materials where light partially traverses the material and gets filtered on its
			way through. Typically this property is specified using a 8-bit gray scale image.
			A value of 1 indicates a fully opaque material whereas 0 equals to a fully transparent
			material. All values in between equal to a partial transparency with the given strength.
			The type of transparency can be specified using the "transparency.type" property.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='transparency.multiplier'>
		<description>
			Defines the multiplier for the transparency texture property. This allows to create
			fading effects with complex transparency. The end result is the transparency value
			multiplied with this value. The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='solidity'>
		<description>
			Defines the solidity material. Transparent materials allow to see through with
			varying strength. In contrary to the transparency texture property the solidity
			defines the probability of light rays actually interacting with the material.
			With transparency material can be fully transparent but still act like a full
			mirror at grazing angles. Solidity on the other hand makes materials truely
			transparent to all light interaction. This can be used for ghost effects or
			fading out objects which is not possible with transparency. Typically this property
			is specified using a 8-bit gray scale image. A value of 1 indicates a fully solid
			material whereas 0 equals to a fully non-solid material. All values in between equal
			to a partial solidity with the given strength. The type of solidity can be specified
			using the "solidity.type" property.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='solidity.masked'>
		<description>
			Defines if the solidity is masked. Some materials do not require the full level of
			solidity support as they contain only holes. Fences are a typical example of such a
			type of material. Often this kind of solidity can be rendered faster than common
			solidity. Using this property the material can be marked as either having full grades
			of solidity or just having holes. With holes solidity values above 0.5 mark solid areas
			while solidity values below 0.5 mark holes which is the default. A value of 0 (or
			below 0.5) marks the material as using all levels of solidity. A value of 1 (or above
			0.5) marks the material as having holes only.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='solidity.multiplier'>
		<description>
			Defines the multiplier for the solidity texture property. This allows to create
			fading effects with complex solidity. The end result is the solidity value
			multiplied with this value. The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='refraction.distort'>
		<description>
			Defines the distortion applied to rendered content behind transparent material.
			The distortion works by manipulating the coordinates of the point to be used as the
			background pixel color using a 2-channel image. The red channel indicates the amount
			of displacement in the x direction (with -1 being 0 red and 1 being full red) and
			the green channel indicates the displacement in the y direction (same as with red).
			The displacement strength is defined using "refraction.distort.strength". Usually a
			3-component image is used where the blue channel has no use. This way normal maps
			can be directly used for distortion.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>2</components>
		<default>
			<red>0.5</red>
			<green>0.5</green>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='refraction.distort.strength'>
		<description>
			Defines the strength of the refraction distortion. Scales the displacement by the
			given single value. Negative values are possible inventing the displacements.
			The displacement is measured relative to the size of the render window. Hence a
			value of 0.1 would cause displacements to have a magnitude of up to 10% of the
			render window size. The default is 0.01 which results in a usual screen resolution
			a displacement of roughly 10 pixels (1% of render window size).
			This is a single value.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0.01</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='reflectivity'>
		<description>
			Defines the reflectivity of a material. A value of 1 fully reflects the environment
			without any diffuse contribution. A value of 0 reflects nothing showing the entire
			diffuse contribution. Values in between represent the amount of reflection of the
			environment. The reflectivity can be defined for each color component individually
			(typical for matrials like gold) or for all at the same time (typical for materials
			like plastic).
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='reflectivity.multiplier'>
		<description>
			Defines the multiplier for the reflectivity. The reflectivity value is first
			multiplied by this value before being send down the lighting pipeline as described
			in "reflectivity". This property is useful for fine adjusting reflectivity without
			altering the source image as well as better using the limited resolution of image
			files especially with low reflectivity values.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='reflectivity.solidity.multiplier'>
		<description>
			Defines the reflectivity weight factor for solidity. This texture property is used
			with decal textures to weight the decal reflectivity against the reflectivity of the
			underlaying geometry. This allows to create decals where not all texture properties
			affect the underlaying geometry the same way in respect to the decal solidity.
			A value of 0 makes the decal to not affect the underlaying geometry reflectivity
			at all. A value of 1 makes the decal fully overwrite the underlaying geometry
			reflectivity. Values in between blend linearly the decal reflectivity with the
			underlaying geometry reflectivity. The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='roughness'>
		<description>
			Defines the roughness of the surface. This value is typically used for defining the
			sharpness of reflections. A value of 0 defines a mirror like smooth surface. A value
			of 1 defines a very rough surface. Values in between create a blend between a smooth
			and a rough surface. Rough surfaces have blurry reflections while smooth surfaces
			have mirror like sharp reflections. The roughness value is comparable to the roughness
			value in the Beckman Shading formula and allows to control the roughness of the
			surface in a more intuitive way. The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='roughness.remap.lower'>
		<description>
			Defines the lower remapping value for the roughness of the surface. The remapping
			allows to use the same roughness input for various skins as well as simplify creating
			art asset by individually remapping the the input values to the new range defined by
			roughness.remap.lower and roughness.remap.upper. A roughness value of 0 is mapped to
			roughness.remap.lower, a value of 1 is mapped to roughness.remap.upper and all values
			in between are mapped linearly. Thus the roughness value can be seen as the blend
			factor between roughness.remap.lower and roughness.remap.upper. The value of this
			property has to be of value type. The default value is 0.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='roughness.remap.upper'>
		<description>
			Defines the upper remapping value for the roughness of the surface. The remapping
			allows to use the same roughness input for various skins as well as simplify creating
			art asset by individually remapping the the input values to the new range defined
			by roughness.remap.lower and roughness.remap.upper. A roughness value of 0 is mapped
			to roughness.remap.lower, a value of 1 is mapped to roughness.remap.upper and all
			values in between are mapped linearly. Thus the roughness value can be seen as the
			blend factor between roughness.remap.lower and roughness.remap.upper. The value of
			this property has to be of value type. The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='roughness.gamma'>
		<description>
			Defines the gamma correction for the roughness property. Typically used for images
			which have a particular gamma value. By default roughness images are considered to
			be real values hence no gamma correction is applied. In some cases though like tools
			creating gamma corrected images setting the usage of a custom gamma correction is
			required. In this case the gamma required to convert the image data to real values
			has to be specified. Gamma correction is applied to the roughness property values
			before remapping is done. The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='roughness.solidity.multiplier'>
		<description>
			Defines the roughness weight factor for solidity. This texture property is used with
			decal textures to weight the decal roughness against the roughness of the underlaying
			geometry. This allows to create decals where not all texture properties affect the
			underlaying geometry the same way in respect to the decal solidity. A value of 0 makes
			the decal to not affect the underlaying geometry roughness at all. A value of 1 makes
			the decal fully overwrite the underlaying geometry roughness. Values in between blend
			linearly the decal roughness  with the underlaying geometry roughness.
			The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='environmentmap'>
		<description>
			Defines the environment map to use for reflection. By default the Graphic Module
			produces and environment map for reflections itself dynamically if it is able to do
			so. Using this property the environment map to use for reflections can be forced.
			This can be used for various purpose. For example by defining static environment maps
			the Graphic Module can be helped to avoid dealing with dynamic environment maps.
			Or it can be used to achieve special effects for example by using a renderable.
			This allows to show foreign environment content like an object reflecting a different
			world.
			<br/><br/>
			This property is typically of image or renderable type. The image has to be of one
			of the supported image types. To use a cube map the image has to have a depth of 6
			with each layer specifying a face of the cube map in the following order:<br/>
			- layer 0: positive x axis<br/>
			- layer 1: negative x axis<br/>
			- layer 2: positive y axis<br/>
			- layer 3: negative y axis<br/>
			- layer 4: positive z axis<br/>
			- layer 5: negative z axis<br/>
			<br/>
			Each layer has to be oriented along the other two positive axes. Hence the positive
			x axis layer has to be oriented with the image x and y axis along the cube map y and
			z axis.
			<br/><br/>
			This property has no default value. If it is not specified the Graphic Module creates
			an environment map itself according to whatever rules it sees fit.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='reflected'>
		<description>
			Defines if geometry with this skin is reflected by other geometry. Typically
			reflections are done using static or dynamic environment maps and optionally other
			real time reflection algorithms. By default all geometry is reflected by other
			geometry and rendered in dynamically rendered environment maps. Editing objects as
			used in the IGDE editors should not be reflected by other geometry and never show
			up in environment maps. This property allows these objects to be not reflected by
			other geometry. This can be also useful in a game situation to make an object not
			to be reflected by other objects. This is typically the case for objects not really
			existing like ghosts or imagined objects. This property is of value type. A value
			of 0.5 or higher makes the geometry to be reflected by other geometry. A value
			below 0.5 prevents the geometry from being reflected by other geometry.
			This default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='mirror'>
		<description>
			Defines that this material is a fully reflective ( perfect ) flat mirror. All pixels
			covered by mesh faces with this texture reflect the world totally. Transparency
			effects like refraction distortion can be applied to mirrors. Use this property
			only on flat or nearly flat geometry. For curved geometry use the "reflection.*"
			properties. Mirror reflections tend to be faster than "reflection.*" reflections
			and should be used if the geometry is flat. A value of 0 equals to no mirror
			reflection. A value of 1 equals to full mirror reflections.
			This is a single value wit default 0.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='emissivity'>
		<description>
			Defines the component wise light emission of a surface. A value of 0 equals to no
			light being emitted from the surface whereas 1 equals to full bright light being
			emitted. In the lighting model used by this game engine there exists no maximum
			strength of light since the light intensity is only limited towards the bottom.
			For this reason the additional property "emissivity.intensity" indicates the maximum
			intensity for all color components. The real intensity equals to the emissivity
			value multiplied by the "emissivity.intensity" value. Usually this property is an
			24-bit color image. The default is black.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='emissivity.tint'>
		<description>
			Defines a color used to tint the emissivity property. This defines an 3-component
			color that is multiplied component wise with the emissivity property. Typically
			used to create tinted versions of a texture without creating multiple skins.
		</description>
		<type>color</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>1</red>
			<green>1</green>
			<blue>1</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='emissivity.intensity'>
		<description>
			Defines the intensity of light emission. This value has the same value range as the
			intensity parameter of light sources. For a common 100W light bulb this value would
			be around 1. This value has to be a single value.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='environmentroom'>
		<description>
			Defines an environment room to use to produce the illusion of a 3 dimensional room
			behind a flat wall. This is typically used to create a more realistic illusion of a
			room behind a window in contrary to flat window textures.
			<br/><br/>
			Environment rooms are environment map type cube or equirectangular texture containing
			a prerendered illusion of a room. The environment room is oriented like this:<br/>
			- x axis: along the texture u direction<br/>
			- y axis: along the negative texture v direction<br/>
			- z axis: along the negative normal direction.<br/>
			<br/>
			The room extends along the x and y axis map to the texture coordinate range from
			0 to 1 in the respective room axis. The size of the room is defined with the
			"environmentroom.size" texture property. The position of the room is half the
			"environmentroom.size" value. The texture coordinates on the flat surface maps to
			the invisible negative z axis face of the room.
			<br/><br/>
			The environment room is used if this texture property is defined. Otherwise normal
			rendering is used
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='environmentroom.size'>
		<description>
			Defines the size ratio of an environment room to use to produce the illusion of a 3
			dimensional room behind a flat wall. See the environmentroom texture property for
			details. The size is a 2 component value larger than 0 representing the ratio between
			the height and width and the depth and width of the room. The first component contains
			the ratio between height and width. The second component contains the ratio between
			the depth and width. The default value is (1,1) defining a cubic room. The actual
			perceived size in metric units depends on the actual texture coordinates used.
			The ratio between the height and width of the texture coordinates has to be identical
			to the first value component.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>2</components>
		<default>
			<red>1</red>
			<green>1</green>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='environmentroom.offset'>
		<description>
			Defines the offset of an environment room cube map relative to the room center.
			This offset is required if the cube map origin is not located exactly at the center
			of the room. This is typically the case for in-engine rendered cube maps used as
			environment room cube maps. Placing the cube map origin near the entry side of the
			room reduces perspective problems. The offset is a 3 component value: x, y, z.
			The default value is (0,0,0).
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='environmentroom.mask'>
		<description>
			Defines the mask of an environment room. The mask defines the blending between the
			environment room and the regular materila parameters. The mask is a 1 component with
			0 showing the regular material parameters and 1 showing only the environment room.
			The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='environmentroom.emissivity'>
		<description>
			Defines the emissivity of an environment room to use to produce the illusion of a 3
			dimensional room behind a flat wall.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='environmentroom.emissivity.tint'>
		<description>
			Defines a color used to tint the environment room emissivity property. This defines
			an 3-component color that is multiplied component wise with the environment room
			emissivity property. Typically used to create tinted versions of a texture without
			creating multiple skins.
		</description>
		<type>color</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>1</red>
			<green>1</green>
			<blue>1</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='environmentroom.emissivity.intensity'>
		<description>
			Defines the intensity of an environment room emissivity texture.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='thickness'>
		<description>
			Defines thickness in meters of material.<br/>
			<br/>
			This property is used if the thickness of the material can not be determined from
			the Model faces itself. This is typically the case for window glass where it is
			common to use double sided model textures. Modules can not calculate the thickness
			in this situation because they lack a matching backwards facing model face.<br/>
			<br/>
			This property is used by the Graphic Module for transparency and absorption
			calculations.<br/>
			<br/>
			This property is used by the Audio Module for transmission loss calculations.<br/>
			<br/>
			This is a single value type property. The default value is 0 indicating no explicit
			thickness defined. Modules will calculate the thickness themselves in this case.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='absorption'>
		<description>
			Defines the absorption strength per component. Affected by absorption.range.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='absorption.range'>
		<description>
			Defines the absorption range. Each component in absorption is multiplied by this value.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='shadow.none'>
		<description>
			Defines if this material does not can shadows. All values above 0.5 prevents this
			material from casting shadows (solid nor transparent). All values below 0.5 cause
			this texture to cast shadows. This is a single value.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='shadow.importance'>
		<description>
			Defines a threshold to stop this texture from casting shadows. This is a performance
			optimization property and is linked to user settings. If the user chooses a high
			detail level this shadow is shown otherwise not. To prevent shadows from being cast
			at all use "shadow.none" instead. A value of 0 equals to the lowest detail level where
			only the most vital textures cast shadows. A value of 1 equals to the highest detail
			level where any textures cast shows. All values in between represent the detail
			percentage (hence 0.2 for example requires the user to set the detail level at or
			above 20% to see this shadow). This is a single value with default 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='hint.nocompression'>
		<description>
			Defines if hardware textures can be compressed or not. Graphic modules can decide to
			compress textures to conserve memory. Compression though tends to have a more or less
			negative impact on the visual quality depending on the kind of texture. Usually
			diffuse textures are compressed while normal textures are not. If you have a special
			texture which has to keep the full quality you can use this property to tell the
			Graphic Module to not compress this texture. As this is a hint the Graphic Module is
			not required to respect it. A value of 0 indicates that this texture can be compressed.
			A value of 1 indicates that this texture should not be compressed if possible.
			This is a single value with default 0.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='texcoord.clamp'>
		<description>
			Defines if texture coordinates are clamped instead of repeated. A value of 0 indicates
			that texture coordinates are repeated. A value of 1 indicates that texture coordinates
			are clamped to the range of 0 to 1. This is a single value with default 0.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='texcoord.offset'>
		<description>
			Defines offset of texture coordinates relative to model texture coordinates.
			This is a color value with 2 components (u, v) with default 0. If multiple
			transformations are used applies first "texcoord.zoom" then "texcoord.rotate"
			then "texcoord.offset".
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>2</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='texcoord.scale'>
		<description>
			Defines scaling of texture coordinates relative to model texture coordinates.
			This is a color value with 2 components (u, v) with default 1. Zooming has as
			center the center of the texture. If multiple transformations are applies first
			"texcoord.zoom" then "texcoord.rotate" then "texcoord.offset".
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>2</components>
		<default>
			<red>1</red>
			<green>1</green>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='texcoord.rotate'>
		<description>
			Defines rotation of texture coordinates relative to model texture coordinates.
			This is a single value with default 0. Rotates texture coordinates counter
			clock wise around the center of the texture. If multiple transformations are
			used applies first "texcoord.zoom" then "texcoord.rotate" then "texcoord.offset".
			Value represents rotation mapped from 0 to 360 degrees to the range from 0 to 1.
			Values larger than 1 or less than 0 are supported. In this case the value is
			normalized into the range from 0 to 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='omnidir.rotate'>
		<description>
			Defines rotation of omni-direction textures relative to model texture coordinates.
			This is a 3-component value with default (0,0,0). Rotates the omni-direction texture
			counter clock wise. Red (first) component is rotation around X axis, green (second)
			component is rotation around Y axis and blue (third) component is rotation around
			Z axis. Values represent rotation mapped from 0 to 360 degrees to the range from 0 to 1.
			Values larger than 1 or less than 0 are supported. In this case the value is
			normalized into the range from 0 to 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='omnidir.rotate.spot'>
		<description>
			Defines rotation of omni-direction textures relative to model texture coordinates
			for spot or projected type light sources only.
			This is a 3-component value with default (0,0,0). Rotates the omni-direction texture
			counter clock wise. Red (first) component is rotation around X axis, green (second)
			component is rotation around Y axis and blue (third) component is rotation around
			Z axis. Values represent rotation mapped from 0 to 360 degrees to the range from 0 to 1.
			Values larger than 1 or less than 0 are supported. In this case the value is
			normalized into the range from 0 to 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='variation.u'>
		<description>
			Defines if texture variations are used along the texture U direction. If texture
			variations are enabled various texture properties can be defines using a depth of
			larger than 1. The integral part of texture coordinates in the U direction is used
			to randomly pick a layer from these properties. A value of 0 indicates that texture
			variations are not used along the U direction. A value of 1 indicates that texture
			variations are used along the U direction. This is a single value with default 0.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='variation.v'>
		<description>
			Defines if texture variations are used along the texture V direction. If texture
			variations are enabled various texture properties can be defines using a depth of
			larger than 1. The integral part of texture coordinates in the V direction is used
			to randomly pick a layer from these properties. A value of 0 indicates that texture
			variations are not used along the V direction. A value of 1 indicates that texture
			variations are used along the V direction. This is a single value with default 0.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='variation.weight'>
		<description>
			Defines the probability weighting of layers for texture variations.
			The probability of a layer to be picked is calculated using the following formula:
			<br/><br/>
			(1 + weight.atPixel(layer,0)) / sum(weights).
			<br/><br/>
			This is a 1 dimensional image with default 0 for all pixels.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='particle.sheets'>
		<description>
			Defines the number of sheets to use for particles of type "beam" or "ribbon".
			This property is only used by Graphic modules supporting advanced particle render
			controls. Otherwise this property is ignored and the graphic module uses an
			appropriate way to render particle beams and ribbons. A value of 0 allows the
			graphic module to choose an appropriate value itself. This is the same as if the
			graphic module does not support this property at all.
			This is a single value with default value 0.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='outline.color'>
		<description>
			Defines the outline color. If outline.thickness is larger than 0 an outline is
			rendered around the component. This is typically used to highlight objects or to
			use cartoon style effects. Outline color is rendered as fully rough material
			with no reflectivity. This allows outline to be affected by lighting like other
			skins which makes outlines fit better.
		</description>
		<type>color</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='outline.color.tint'>
		<description>
			Defines a color used to tint the outline.color property. This defines an 3-component
			color that is multiplied component wise with the color property. Typically used to
			create tinted versions of a texture without creating multiple skins.
		</description>
		<type>color</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>1</red>
			<green>1</green>
			<blue>1</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='outline.thickness'>
		<description>
			Defines the outline thickness in meters or percentage of camera field-of-view
			depending on the value of "outline.thickness.screen". If the "outline.thickness.screen"
			value is 0 this value is measured as meters in world space. Otherwise the value is
			measured relative to the camera field-of-view which makes the thickness to stay at
			the same visual size no matter what distance it is looked at. For example in the
			screen mode a value of 0.01 for example equals to a thickness of 1% the screen width.
			If thickness is larger than 0 an outline is rendered around the component. This is
			typically used to highlight objects or to use cartoon style effects.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='outline.thickness.screen'>
		<description>
			Determines if the outline thickness is relative to screen. If this value is 0
			the "outline.thickness" value is measured as meters in world space. If this value
			is 1 the "outline.thickness" value is measured as percentage of the camera
			field-of-view resulting in the visual thickness to stay the same no matter the
			distance to the object. For example in this mode a value of 0.01 for example
			equals to a thickness of 1% the screen width.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='outline.solidity'>
		<description>
			Defines the outline solidity. If outline.thickness is larger than 0 an outline is
			rendered around the component. This is typically used to highlight objects or to
			use cartoon style effects. The solidity can be used to create transparent outlines.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='outline.emissivity'>
		<description>
			Defines the outline emissivity color. If outline.thickness is larger than 0 an
			outline is rendered around the component. This is typically used to highlight
			objects or to use cartoon style effects. While outline.color is affected by
			lighting emissivity is not. This allows to make glowing outlines. If you use
			this texture property you have to also use outline.emissivity.intensity
			otherwise you will get no visible emissivity.
		</description>
		<type>color</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='outline.emissivity.tint'>
		<description>
			Defines a color used to tint the outline.emissivity property. This defines an
			3-component color that is multiplied component wise with the outline.emissivity
			property. Typically used to create tinted versions of a texture without creating
			multiple skins.
		</description>
		<type>color</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>1</red>
			<green>1</green>
			<blue>1</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='outline.emissivity.intensity'>
		<description>
			Defines the outline emissivity intensity. If outline.thickness is larger than 0 an
			outline is rendered around the component. This is typically used to highlight objects
			or to use cartoon style effects. This value has the same value range as the
			intensity parameter of light sources. For a common 100W light bulb this value would
			be around 1. This value has to be a single value.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='rim.emissivity'>
		<description>
			Defines the component wise rim light emission of a surface. Rim light intensity
			is multiplied by the angle difference between the camera view plane and the
			surface normal. This allows to create ghost like effects where objects glow
			along their rim while not glowing seen face on.<br/>
			<br/>
			A value of 0 equals to no light being emitted whereas 1 equals to full bright
			light being emitted. In the lighting model used by this game engine there exists
			no maximum strength of light since the light intensity is only limited towards
			the bottom. For this reason the additional property "rim.emissivity.intensity"
			indicates the maximum intensity for all color components. The real intensity
			equals to the emissivity value multiplied by the "rim.emissivity.intensity"
			value.<br/>
			<br/>
			Usually this property is an 24-bit color image. The default is black.
		</description>
		<type>image</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>0</red>
			<green>0</green>
			<blue>0</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='rim.emissivity.tint'>
		<description>
			Defines a color used to tint the rim emissivity property. This defines
			a 3-component color that is multiplied component wise with the
			rim.emissivity property. Typically used to create tinted versions of a
			texture without creating multiple skins.
		</description>
		<type>color</type>
		<components>3</components>
		<default>
			<red>1</red>
			<green>1</green>
			<blue>1</blue>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='rim.emissivity.intensity'>
		<description>
			Defines the intensity of rim light emission. This value has the same value
			range as the intensity parameter of light sources. For a common 100W light
			bulb this value would be around 1. This value has to be a single value.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='rim.angle'>
		<description>
			Defines the maximum angle difference between the camera view plane and the
			surface normal for rim light emissivity to become 0. Surface normals
			located in the camera view plane (parallel to this plane) have maximum
			intensity. The intensity is faded until reaching rim.angle deviation from
			the camera view plane. The rim.exponent defines the shape of the fading curve.<br/>
			<br/>
			The angle value is defined as mapping between no deviation (0 degrees) at
			value 0 to full deviation (90 degrees) at value 1. The default value is 0
			which disables the effect.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='rim.exponent'>
		<description>
			Defines the shape of the fading curve for rim light. The value is used
			as exponent for the curve. Hence a value of 1 produces a linear blend
			along the angle (constant intensity change per degree change).
			A value of 2 produces a squared shape with intensity changing stronger
			near rim.angle and less near 0 angle. A value of 0.5 produces a similar
			squared shape but flipped with intensity changing stronger near 0 angle
			and less near rim.angle . The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>graphic</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='bounciness'>
		<description>
			Defines the bounciness of a surface. This is used by the physics module to determine
			with what fraction of the incoming force an object is repelled from a surface.
			A value of 0 equals to no bounciness in which case an object hitting this surface
			is not repelled at all whereas 1 equals to full bounciness in which case an object
			bounces off this surface with the force it arrived. This has to be a single value.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0.2</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>physics</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='sound.none'>
		<description>
			Defines if the material is interacting with sound at all. This texture property can
			be make objects become ghost-like to sound as well as helping Audio Modules optimize
			processing time. The value is of single value type and has to be 0 for regular sound
			processing or 1 to not affect sound processing. The default value is 0.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>audio</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='sound.absorption'>
		<description>
			Defines the sound absorption of a surface. This property is used by the audio
			module to determine the fraction of sound energy absorbed by the surface.
			The value is of single value type and has to be in the range from 0 to 1.
			A value of 0 absorbs no sound while a value of 1 absorbs all sound.
			The default value is 0.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0.12</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>audio</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='sound.absorption.lower'>
		<description>
			Defines the scaling factor to apply to "sound.absorption" for low frequencies.
			The scale factor changes linearly from lower to upper value depending on frequency.
			The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0.35</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>audio</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='sound.absorption.upper'>
		<description>
			Defines the scaling factor to apply to "sound.absorption" for tones of high
			frequencies. The scale factor changes linearly from lower to upper value
			depending on frequency. The default value is 1.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>1.75</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>audio</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='sound.transmission'>
		<description>
			Defines the required thickness in meters of material before sound drops to inaudible
			levels. This property is used by the audio module to determine the transmission loss
			for sound passing through material after applying absorption. The reflected sound
			energy is the remaining amount of sound energy after absorption and transmission.
			Hence if you want a fully reflective wall set transmission to 0.<br/>
			<br/>
			The thickness of a material is defined as the distance between the model face where
			the sound enters the surface and the first model face it exits. Faces are classified
			using the orientation of their face normal compared to the sound travel direction:<br/>
			<br/>
			- Entering faces: face normal points in the opposite direction<br/>
			- Exiting faces: face normal points in the same direction<br/>
			<br/>
			Another way to look at it would be saying "entering faces" point towards the sound
			wave while "exiting faces" point away from the sound wave.<br/>
			<br/>
			The "exiting faces" are not required to be located in the same Component resource.
			Actually in most of the situations this is not the case.<br/>
			<br/>
			If no "exiting face" exists the thickness is considered to be infinite and sound
			waves are inaudible.<br/>
			<br/>
			The property value is of single value type and has to be 0 or larger. With a value of
			0 sound passing through the material is always inaudible. For larger values the sound
			volume drops linear with distance travelled in the material.<br/>
			<br/>
			The "sound.transmission.lower" and "sound.transmission.upper" properties are
			multipliers for this property for different frequency ranges.<br/>
			<br/>
			The default value is 0.4 which equals a 40cm thick brickwork wall plastered on both sides.<br/>
			<br/>
			Typical values:<br/>
			- Brickwork plastered both sides: 0.4<br/>
			- Brickwork plastered one side: 0.92<br/>
			- Wood studs (38/89mm) 20mm Gypsum both sides: 0.78<br/>
			- 6mm double glass with air-gap: 0.7<br/>
			- 75mm timber studs plastered both sides: 1.2<br/>
			<br/>
			Reasonable range values can be calculated from engineering charts for sound
			transmission using this approximation: range = thickness * pow(2, -reductionDB/6) * 1024.<br/>
			Units are: range(m), thickness(m), reductionDB(dB). 1024 is 1/pow(2,-60[dB]/6).<br/>
			<br/>
			Note: Double Sided Geometry<br/>
			To simulate a material like air-gap double window glass done using double sided model
			textures use "sound.transmission" with a value of 0.7 and a "thickness" of 0.1.
			This values are from the above table. This creates a material with constant sound
			transmission effect transmitting 1/7 of sound volume to the other side.<br/>
			<br/>
			Note: No Transmission Loss<br/>
			To simulate a material with no transmission loss use "sound.none" if there is no
			absorption or a large value like 1000 if there is absorption.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0.4</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>audio</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='sound.transmission.lower'>
		<description>
			Defines the scaling factor to apply to "sound.transmission" for low frequencies.
			The scale factor changes linearly from lower to upper value depending on frequency.
			Walls typically filter out higher frequencies allowing lower frequencies to pass easily.
			<br/><br/>
			The default value is 2.8 which equals to a reduction of noise reduction capability
			of the material by 9dB.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>2.8</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>audio</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
	
	<property name='sound.transmission.upper'>
		<description>
			Defines the scaling factor to apply to "sound.transmission" for high frequencies.
			The scale factor changes linearly from lower to upper value depending on frequency.
			Walls typically filter out higher frequencies allowing lower frequencies to pass easily.
			<br/><br/>
			The default value is 0.28 which equals to an increase of noise reduction capability
			of the material by 11dB (empirical engineering value). Higher values increase the
			high-pass filter effect. A value of 1 removes the low-pass filter effect.
		</description>
		<type>value</type>
		<components>1</components>
		<default>
			<value>0.28</value>
		</default>
		<affects>
			<module>audio</module>
		</affects>
	</property>
</texturePropertyList>
